my thumbnail is the antique thumbnail
it's the let's look as ridiculous as
possible I'm tired and I'm still wanting
to go in and periscope and go live
tonight cuz I had fun last by doing it
and I'm gonna do it with my brain in the
current state you see uh it looks like
it's light outside it is not that is my
light shining out of my curtains my
light above is burnt out so this is what
I have currently it's our person there's
a person watching normally that doesn't
happen on here because I just came on
live to update so today I spent the day
creating a different YouTube channel
than this one I'm still going to be
doing the daily videos on this one for
the global cooperative for how we create
a better economy and the bigger vision
but I started the idea cafe channel so
that we can have the conversation piece
so every Wednesday at 11:00 a.m. Pacific
Standard Time me and three to four other
people are going to meet and have a
conversation about a meaningful question
the idea is eventually we will open up
more and more time slots as people want
to be on camera and answer the question
so that eventually it's going 24/7 with
clearly not me in all of the
conversations but it's not within my
capacity and I already have the people
lined up for this Wednesday so that is
the only thing that is hoping happening
on the I say hope cafe idea cafe it's
called idea cafe it used to be called
pub cafe and so that is what I was doing
today and so although I didn't think I
was overdoing it I am now in a state of
having overdone it for the day so I just
wanted to come on because I like this
equipment of doing a daily video and
although I did do a video today I did
the introduction video to the idea cafe
including a thumbnail and everything
which this channel doesn't get because I
can't do one daily I'm allowed to do
like three a month or something for free
and even that too many too much energy
you to create as I have to deal with
technology that I do not like I am
interacting more and more with people on
YouTube in comments I'm hoping and I get
more subscribers here there's currently
I got one single subscriber who my other
one evil I just created it today which
makes me happy and I have like I said I
already other participants actually have
like seven participants already so this
is the one where when I put it out on my
on my Facebook group there was for
people who are like yeah that sounds fun
I want to be involved as opposed to up
to this point where I'm explaining like
the big vision and I feel like it's like
pulling teeth but like yeah sure you can
just bounce like capitalism and create a
world that works for everyone sounds
great let me know when it's done
where as being part of a conversation
and showcasing what that actually looks
like I just I love everything about it
because we're going to once we've done
it for a few weeks we can show what that
looks like and I'm then gonna reach out
to YouTube people with subscribers
casual subscribers to invite them to be
part of it and then they will bring some
of their subscribers with them and also
inviting people who have no subscribers
because we can um help them generate
them especially people who might be
doing what I'm doing talking about world
issues talking about things that matter
that aren't necessarily historically
bringing in the subscribers so I want to
keep this under five minutes I just
wanted to come on quickly and update I
should have gone why didn't I use it I'm
gonna come on live again tomorrow at
some point because I want to test out
the stream yard on YouTube I've done it
on periscope and I like it but I've yet
to do it on stream yard I honestly
didn't excited think anyone would be
actually joining in as there usually
aren't people the odd time I go live on
here just like a live on periscope I
will see you tomorrow a better world
it's on its way they brought to you by
our diversity and all the goodness and
kittens and unicorns of the world and
please like see like and subscribe I
will see you tomorrow